<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on very cool blog</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on very cool blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:15:43 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Comptia A&#43;</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/comptia-a&#43;/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:15:43 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/comptia-a&#43;/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So I recently found out the legend himself Professor Messer started uploading videos for the new CompTIA A+ exam that came out this last March. I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to get this cert for a while so with me having more free time and content that I can study, I think this is the perfect time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From what I read the content of the old and new exam are very similar, and the videos I&amp;rsquo;ve watched from Professor Messer a while back will still be useful. My current goal will be to have it done by the end of this month, however this might change depending on how much I have to study. The official site says they recommend &amp;lsquo;9 to 12 months hands-on experience in the lab or field&amp;rsquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m going to be taking it with none. That&amp;rsquo;s about it really. I&amp;rsquo;ll more than likely make another post when I receive it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Site Pain</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/site-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:08:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/site-pain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have spent way too much time on this crap. I have no idea why it didn&amp;rsquo;t work before, but it&amp;rsquo;s working now. This whole site is hanging on a thread it&amp;rsquo;s hilarious. I am begging for nothing to break when I upload this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At first the issue was it constantly bringing me to localhost:1313 everytime I clicked on &amp;ldquo;very cool blog&amp;rdquo;, instead of the main page. It took forever and a lot of hard-coding but eventually it was sort of working.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
